Kateryna Butsnieva

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

(512) 888-4419



butsnieva@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/butsnieva In



butsnieva.dev



github.com/butsnieva



Education and Certifications

The University of Texas

Coding bootcamp Certificate Sep 2021

SI Computer School

"SQA Professional" Certificate Jun 2020

Prydniprovska State Academy of Civil Architecture and Engineering

Bachelor's degree in Architecture May 2017

Computer Academy "STEP"

Software Development, Software Engineering Dec 2014

Technical skills

Languages:

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python

Database Management:

MySQL, Sequelize, MongoDB, Mongoose

Libraries/Frameworks:

¡Query, React.js, Express.js, Bootstrap, UiKit, Tailwind, Selenium, webdriver.io

Other Technologies:

Node.is, Socket.io, Handlebars, Git, Bash

Summary

Ambitious Full Stack Web Developer, effective at using the latest technologies to create efficient and maintainable back-end interfaces and approachable user experiences. Holding a certificate from the University of Texas Coding Bootcamp.

Brings 4+ years of professional experience in QA Testing, ability to design and develop web applications across multiple APIs, third-party integrations and databases.

Projects

mvJober

Deployed: https://my-jober.web.app | Repo: https://github.com/butsnieva/myJober

Full-stack web application that allows users to post short-term jobs they need help with, and also accept jobs that other users have posted.

Built with: React, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB

Experience

QA Engineer

SI Global Solutions | Austin, TX | Mar, 2019 - Current

- Performed Exploratory testing, Functional, Ad-hoc, Usability, Smoke testing, API testing, Regression, and Database validation testing
- Involved in all Agile ceremonies such as planning, stand up, grooming, retrospective.
- Involved in Mobile Web and Native Mobile APP testing on Android, iPad and iPhone, Emulator, Simulator to perform functional, usability, compatibility testing.
- Created and maintained automated regression test scripts using Selenium WebDriver with JavaScript webdriver.io, Chai and Mocha frameworks.
- Coached and assisted new employees with adapting to processes.

QA Analyst II

B.WELL | Austin, TX | Oct, 2020 - Mar, 2021

- Performed smoke, functional, integration, compatibility, regression, GUI and release acceptance testing of daily builds on web and mobile devices for Healthcare application.
- Developed test cases for new and existing features.
- Verified FHIR data population and accuracy.
- Validated Mastercard's new identity verification service in user's registration process.
- Focused on Medical Record Connections and Health Summary experiences.

Chief Operation Officer (2,5y), <- Sales Manager (9mo)

Global Trans USA | Austin, TX | Jan, 2017 - Jan, 2020

- Mentor and interact with members of staff at all levels.
- Creating, improving, implementing, and enforcing policies and procedures of the organization that will improve operational and financial effectiveness of the company.
- Evaluation of potential mergers, acquisitions, and partnerships.
- Raised profits by 46% within the first 8 months through planning.

Manual QA Tester

"CITRUS" Online Gadget Store | Odessa, Ukraine | Feb, 2014 - Mar, 2016

- Responsible for carrying out manual, integration, and compatibility testing for Citrus ecommerce web and mobile web applications.
- Documented test reports and defect reports and presenting conclusions to the team.
- Participated in the defect review board meetings and weekly team meetings to give and get status updates on the working objectives.